Now that the base is on, I'm going to move on to the lid color.
I did a very natural base, a matte color.
Kind of a yogurt vanilla color.
For the lid, I'm going to something a little more dramatic.
I'm going to use a cranberry color and it's got a lot of shimmer to it and vibrance.
This is very similar color as we're using on the lips.
Kind of a glossy burgundy color.
I'm going to do it very lightly.
I'm actually going to use a fluffier brush that I would normally use on the crease because I don't want it to be so concentrated on the lid.
I just want it to blend and just give kind of a shimmery hint.
I'm putting it on the lid of the eye.
By the lid of the eye, I mean the ball of the eye, which is where the eye ball protrudes.
I'm just kind of dusting it over the lid up to the crease.
You don't want to go any further than this.
You want to get as close to the lash line as possible as well.
Just blend, blend, blend.
I'm kind of buffing it to the eye lid.
I want to see it, but I don't want it to be so dramatic that it takes away from the rest of the look.
Again, I'm not going any further than here because I want this to be kind of the highlight color and to be lighter.
Open and look up.
If you've got some underneath the eye, that's fine.
No big deal.
Just kind of blend it in and clean it up later.
If you get a little bit underneath that's fine because like I said, what I do on top, I like to do underneath.
Close your eye.
Keep it closed.
That's where the lid ends.
Highlight and lid.